<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - Junk Muffler</title>
        <link>https://JunkMuffler.com/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | Junk Muffler</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>All Rights Reserved</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 18:38:38 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://JunkMuffler.com/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Changes Are Afoot - Temporary Hiatus and a New Direction</title>
    <link>https://JunkMuffler.com/posts/changes-and-hiatus/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 18:38:38 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://JunkMuffler.com/posts/changes-and-hiatus/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Hey Junkyard Dogs! Things are going to be quiet for a bit. This is partially for personal reasons, and partially because I want to take Junk Muffler in a different direction.
This means my posts are going to be even less frequent than normal for a while. I&rsquo;m not done. I didn&rsquo;t quit. I have a clear vision for the future of JM.
Sigh&hellip; Let me just tell you what&rsquo;s going on.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Warning Bells</title>
    <link>https://JunkMuffler.com/posts/warning-bells/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 20:00:17 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://JunkMuffler.com/posts/warning-bells/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[When I was a strapping young lad during the early days of the internet, there was an incredible flash game called Don&rsquo;t Sh*t Your Pants. The significance of this game on my life cannot be overstated. It altered the course of history.
This song is an attempt to take the life lessons learned from this 90&rsquo;s flash game and package it up for you in a festive musical fashion.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Twelve Twenty-Six</title>
    <link>https://JunkMuffler.com/posts/twelve-twenty-six/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 20:00:17 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://JunkMuffler.com/posts/twelve-twenty-six/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[As a kid I never believed in Santa Claus. I grew up super poor. My parents wanted to make for darn sure I knew they bought every gift. I don&rsquo;t blame them. The alternative is believing Santa loves rich kids more.
As an adult I&rsquo;ve grown increasingly cynical of Christmas. Not the spirit of it so much. More the execution. I don&rsquo;t understand why showing each other we care has to manifest itself in consumerism.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Danger is Subjective</title>
    <link>https://JunkMuffler.com/posts/danger-is-subjective/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 23:00:17 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://JunkMuffler.com/posts/danger-is-subjective/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Oh fart jokes&hellip; You never get old.
One day I fear my inner 11-year-old will die and fart jokes will cease to be funny. Fortunately that has yet to be the case. This is much to the chagrin of Mrs. Muffler. Fart jokes, it seems, are eternal.
Most of my songs are based on real life. I assure you that I did not sh*t my pants in the middle of a Walmart.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>The Thanksgiving Song</title>
    <link>https://JunkMuffler.com/posts/the-thanksgiving-song/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 22:40:17 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://JunkMuffler.com/posts/the-thanksgiving-song/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Has it seriously been eight months since I released a song? That doesn&rsquo;t seem to be right, but here we are. The YouTube timestamps don&rsquo;t lie.
Wow&hellip;
To be fair, a lot of stuff has happened in my life. I&rsquo;ll hopefully share more about it soon. I may make the musical equivelant of candy corn, but I bust my butt on every song. It takes a lot out of me, even though I love it.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Frames Win Games</title>
    <link>https://JunkMuffler.com/posts/frames-win-games/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 18:24:17 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://JunkMuffler.com/posts/frames-win-games/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I love video games. The problem is I profoundly suck at them. Except for Mario Kart. I&rsquo;m fairly competent at Mario Kart. :)
I didn&rsquo;t play a lot games as a kid. Every year I&rsquo;d beg for a Nintendo. Eventually I was given an old school gray and white Game Boy. I loved that thing. I only had a few games for it. One of them was Tiny Toon Adventures: Bab&rsquo;s Big Break.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Like and Subscribe: Junk Muffler Vol. 1</title>
    <link>https://JunkMuffler.com/posts/like-and-subscribe-junk-muffler-vol-1/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 14:23:38 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://JunkMuffler.com/posts/like-and-subscribe-junk-muffler-vol-1/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I&rsquo;m super-hype to announce the first Junk Muffler album ever! Hopefully it&rsquo;s the first of many more to come. It took me a long time to come up with a collection I was happy with. I hope you enjoy listening to it as much as I enjoyed creating it.
You can find it on all major streaming services. Find yours on the list below and use the link to start blasting this through your headphones!]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Counting Calories</title>
    <link>https://JunkMuffler.com/posts/counting-calories-lullaby/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 14:09:51 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://JunkMuffler.com/posts/counting-calories-lullaby/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Here&rsquo;s a lullaby for all my fellow foodies. Also&hellip; For anyone who managed to survive 2020. I feel like since March all anyone I know has done is sit and eat. I know I gained a bunch of pandemic weight that I&rsquo;m working to get off.
I will say that my weakness in breakfast food. In particular, I LOVE pancakes. Before the pandemic hit we did the &ldquo;Tour du Pancakes&rdquo; where I ate at several local restaurants.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Like and Subscribe: The Musical!</title>
    <link>https://JunkMuffler.com/posts/like-and-subscribe/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 18:03:19 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://JunkMuffler.com/posts/like-and-subscribe/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I feel like subtlety is so undervalued in the music world. Like&hellip; What is a song really about? What&rsquo;s the artist&rsquo;s core message? What do they want you to take away from the song?
In case you missed it, the message of this song is to like and subscribe y&rsquo;all&hellip; Like and subscribe.
Fun fact about how I make music&hellip; The songs I make are usually driven by Music Weeklies.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Compost Lunch</title>
    <link>https://JunkMuffler.com/posts/compost-lunch/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 20:00:21 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://JunkMuffler.com/posts/compost-lunch/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Mrs. Muffler&rsquo;s Composting Isn&rsquo;t All Bad I love to poke fun at Mrs. Muffler, but the truth is we should all be better to the environment.
I&rsquo;m more of a hippie than I let on. We&rsquo;ve both been proud vegetarians for over a decade. I believe the way we treat each other, our planet, and other species matters.
I&rsquo;ll leave the matter there. I create comedy not commentary.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
